[Music]
hi I'm here to drop off my kid sure I'll
take that rat from you uh where is the
other daycare teacher I'm the substitute
got a problem no not at all okay JJ have
fun I'll see you
later what are you staring
[Music]
at this baby is annoying you're going in
time
[Music]
out hey I remember you you're going to
get it
today all right infants it's time for
your intense training I'll de with you
later start with a 100 jumping
[Music]
jacks faster faster be great grateful
I'm not giving you weights as
well now give me 50
push-ups hands up 10 minutes starts
now jeez this woman is too hard on us we
need to get out of here but I need an
ally
H
Bingo Hey kid yeah you
I know we haven't settled our
differences but I know we both don't
like this
teacher put your arms back
up how about you work with me good
gather all the kids when we meet
outside huh no
talking here's what we're going to do uh
you can put your hand down now they're
stuck okay
anyways and then we're out y'all
understand
good uh-huh yeah I get it okay time to
break out I just want you guys to know
if we don't make it out I still don't
like you guys uh-huh yeah all these
little rats are so annoying now's our
chance let's
[Music]
go we're almost there
not so fast I didn't go through 20 years
of military training just to be fooled
by Bratz but you're forgetting one thing
it's five of us and one of you get
her it's not
funny bye-bye
JJ
o JJ you forgot your show and
[Music]
H see you
later okay everyone put your show and
tell items
[Music]
away oh no I forgot today was sh and
tell okay kids come back for story time
and the lion said to the zebra like the
video
please I still need to show and
tell oh I know what I'll
[Music]
do hm what's this oh cool it's an
airplane I'll just use this for my show
and
H I'll just hide it right
here and the bunny said so please
subscribe to the crystalline Gamers the
end okay kids it's show and tell time go
get your
items what's wrong
Pablo what you can't find your Show and
Tell
[Music]
teacher Pao can't find a show and tell
is that
so ooh ooh I can be a detective and find
who sto bu it and when I find who did it
I'm going
to okay calm down Masha let's ask
everybody yay
uh-oh did you steal it did you steal it
you did did you steal it
Masha did you steal it no are you sure
about that yes where were you during
story time I was in the back now leave
me alone hey
h I'm sorry Pablo but we have to start
show and tell
[Music]
now hey watch this this is my monkey he
can talk and he can lift up a whole
house okay Masha that's enough boss baby
it's your
turn this is my
[Music]
airplane what's wrong he said boss baby
took his show and tell no he's lying
this is
mine hey get in
Pablo that's enough I'll go check the
cameras
[Music]
uh-oh boss baby you stole from Pablo
H give it back to him
[Music]
here next time you make an oopsie please
come tell
me you're new here what's your
name that's so cool and very long I'm
having a play dat today want to come
JJ you're invited
[Music]
too just kidding you're
invited what about me uh no you can't
come cuz you're a tattletail hm who
wants to go
anyways boss baby your mom is here okay
see you guys later but not you
Masha JJ it's time for you to
go
[Music]
oh I forgot today is your play date I'll
drop you off right
[Music]
now hi JJ hi I'll be back later to pick
him up all right let's go
upstairs everyone's already here o ooh
let's play
tag oh yeah let me show you guys my new
computer now let me show you guys my
favorite
[Music]
YouTubers I'm going to like the video
and you should too so who wants to go
first
oh no you guys broke my new computer why
would you do that tell me why would you
do
[Music]
that calm down Theodore what happened
mom they broke my computer let me see if
I can fix
[Music]
it all fixed yay thanks
Mom
[Music]
hear
it okay kids it's time to come in I'll
miss
you and the doggy said no I'm not a frog
I'm a NATO chip so please subscribe to
the crystalline
Gamers the
end okay kids I'll see you next week oh
and don't forget tomorrow is JJ's
birthday wow tomorrow's your birthday
are you having a
party wa can I come come on we're
friends now what do you
say okay great hi JJ it's time to
go bye JJ see you
[Music]
tomorrow JJ wake up and come
downstairs Happy Birthday
J look your friends are
here guys chuckecheese is
here hey kids let's have some
fun
man I'm hungry I wonder if they have any
[Music]
snacks
h o
[Music]
cake go JJ it's your birthday go JJ it's
your
birthday yum that was delicious okay
everyone it's cake
time
uh-oh
where's the
cake there's no cake sorry
JJ wow that's sad who would do
[Music]
that I'm sorry I was just hungry I
didn't mean to do
it I said I'm sorry hold on good night
no wait please hey JJ I got you another
cake pH that was a close
one hi I'm here to drop off my kid and
my dog there's no dogs allowed okay
that's fine bye JJ I'll see you
later it's
[Laughter]
[Music]
I'll keep
this I'll take this as
well what a
bully everyone let's go up outside
outside outside outside everybody
[Music]
[Applause]
outside who did
that
BR do you know who I am I'm the boss
baby and you're going to get
it okay kids it's nap
time you got lucky this
[Music]
[Applause]
time
[Music]
Wicky
wakey ouch hey watch it what are you
doing stop it
Mommy oh
yeah oh yeah
okay kids it's time for nap
time I hate nap time yeah we're not even
tired come on guys that'ss now yeah I'm
not going to sleep me too everyone go to
sleep
now I'm going to
play
[Music]
yeah
JJ do you know the answer
uh okay class it's lunchtime come back
after for your
test boss baby is that you you could
call me boss boy now we're all grown up
Masha where is Pablo not cool dude I'm
right here forget that JJ you didn't
turn out too good you're the one to talk
you're steel
Ball but for real how did we get here
weren't we just in daycare yeah I like
this better no more nap time but
apparently now we have a test what's a
test a test is what people take to prove
you're smart that's easy boss baby I
mean boss boy this is serious yeah I
heard if you do bad you go to jail no
Masha I think it's that
bad well that's the Bell see you on
class okay y'all start the
test uh-oh I don't know this JJ yeah
what's the answer to number 1 to 10 I
don't
know huh teacher boss boy and JJ are
cheating that's not good I'm calling the
police oh
no no I don't want to go to jail no
please help JJ wake up your mom is here
bye boss
baby it's boss
[Music]
boy okay I'll go get the kids all righty
okay everybody pay attention today we
have Mr T he's going to give you guys
swim
[Music]
[Applause]
lessons hello everyone my name is Mr T
I'll be showing you guys how to swim but
before we do that I need to tell you
guys the four pool rules there would be
five but I only have four
fingers rule number one no
running rule number two no
diving
rule number three no pushing and Rule
Number Four no
pooping
e any questions why are you pink haha
sunburn okay everyone meet me at the
pool all right guys this is what we're
going to do I'll be in the pool and you
guys will slide down one by one okay
everyone back up I'm going
first Yahoo
JJ you're up
next okay Zoe
yay we'll try again Zoe okay okay it's
your turn
Pablo Pablo why are you crying
[Music]
again you're scared to go into the
pool you can't swim
it's okay Pablo I can't swim either but
I'm still going to try let's go
together well here I
[Music]
go see it's not that
bad you guys can go again if you want to
all right one at a
[Music]
time you're still here go man
oops Mr T say Pablo huh oh
no
gotcha pH that was close boss baby you
didn't follow the rules you're getting
time out oh
man okay kids today we're going to visit
our new
daycare okay everyone settle down R your
coloring books while I go get the
bus I can't wait to see the new daycare
me too I heard there's a big super duper
slide my monkey can probably pick it up
you're lying no I'm not okay kids the
bus is here come outside outside
outside we are are here let's go on a
tour this is the library this is the
kitchen and this is the lunch area this
is the resting area and finally the play
area told you there's a big super duper
slide okay kids go explore while I take
this phone
call man I'm starving oh I know a secret
candy stash really yeah follow me
wee
Yahoo that was
epic this
way it's up
here taada see told you wo
candy this is very sugary and
delicious wow I have so much energy
let's go on the slide
[Music]
again
wao your powers got
activated cool let's see what you can
[Music]
do are y'all coming oh no the
playground's on fire teacher teacher not
now
[Music]
Masha it's not
working teacher Masha what is
it what's going
on oh no everybody go
outside hi we need a firefighter
unsubscribed to the crystalline Gamers
Lane all finished
hooray
yeah and I told my cat not to do it
anymore but he keeps doing
it hey kids today someone new will be
joining us so make sure you be nice to
her okay cool another girl yay I hope
she likes
business I hope she likes the
[Music]
troll n
I hope she likes
[Music]
animals yeah me too bye
mommy
huh um ma'am the high school is across
the street be quiet and get away from my
face you know have to tell me twice
everybody this is Janice she looks like
she's been lifting way pleas what did
you say chill man I mean woman I didn't
say anything you better not you big head
she's a little mean yeah I agree with
you it's playtime and after we will eat
our snacks
yay give me
that
loser have you beaten level 24 yet I
love my monkey I love my monkey I love
my monkey so very much hi Janice give me
that
hey I'll take
[Music]
this okay kids it's snack
time give me your cookie but that's mine
I don't
care give me that no give me me that you
big head no here just take mine I don't
want
it I'll be back for your
lunch we'll see about that it's recess
time I'm here to call a meeting about
the mean girl yeah she took my monkey
she took my cookie yeah she yelled at me
yeah and she made fun of my head well
your head is kind of big boss
baby anyways this is what we're going to
do hey Big Head come give me a push who
me yes
you push me don't mind if I
[Applause]
[Music]
do give it to me
no be quiet my monkey can lift up a
house no it
can't stop it
guys get off the
table come back here that's it everyone
time
[Music]
out our teacher is so mean yeah she
won't let us do whatever we want no
she's not but she's always nice to us
Bobby get off the crib see our point
she's just concerned for your safety
whatever she's still mean their timeout
is over let me go tell them hey
[Music]
guys oh my gosh the teacher I'll call
the
ambulance okay kids The Substitute is on
on her way make sure you be
[Music]
nice finally she's
[Applause]
gone what's
that hello kids my name is Miss bigy and
I'm here to substitute you we're going
to have so much fun in day
care she's funny yes I like her okay
kids settle down I'm going to read you a
story why is she still singing it's fine
I like it once upon a time a chicken
nugget
de not a chicken I'm subscrib to The
crystaline Gamers and like the
video you're right Bobby she won't stop
um Miss Piggy can you stop singing
please this is The Song That Never Ends
you will hear it even in your bed
forever and ever and forever it goes on
and on my
friends I can't take it anymore it's
been 3
hours yeah we got to do something about
it I agree
H oh I have an idea we'll glue her trap
shut
[Music]
yeah um Miss Piggy all that thinging
must make you thirsty here try
[Music]
this and don't come back
hi kids what did I
miss we missed you so much
[Music]
hahaa I want to see it okay kids the bus
is here line up for our field
trip hey bus baby cut it no I didn't yes
you did cut it is not even a word okay
kids no fight
get in the
[Music]
Buss and and McDonald a e e i okay kids
we're
here I'm Peppa
[Music]
Pig and this is how you dig it looks
like chocolate Masha don't eat
it Okay who wants to ride horses ooh ooh
me first no me okay you can both go
yay ready set I'm going to win no I'm
going to win
go I won that no I did sh sh you wish I
want a rematch in your dreams who's next
me okay
Zoe Pablo what about
[Music]
you Pablo come back hey JJ you should go
on the horse and test your skills no he
can't do that the teacher isn't here
mind your own business I'm telling the
teacher Masha wait great not everyone's
gone this is your
[Music]
chance see it's not so bad now go get
him
[Music]
tiger I'm coming
JJ hold
on sorry about
that the bus they left without us let's
go
[Music]
okay everyone I have an announcement
I'll be in a long meeting after lunch so
today you guys will be watching an
educational
program who want to watch an educational
program that's boring no it's not okay
follow me to the media
room this is Amanda the adventurer okay
kids the show will start in a minute I
got to go to the meeting now I'll be
right
back hi I'm Amanda I love apples do you
like apples ew I hate apples I like
apples that's okay you should never be
afraid to try something new if you say
so do you know where the store is no do
you know where the store is H This
Girl's Crazy she keeps repeating herself
we don't know the answer just tell us do
you know where the store is what the
look look the store is right there
that's right let's go hello meatman can
you tell the meatman what we need grass
can you tell the meatman what we need
cookie tell him what we need me that's
right this is getting
creepy I want to go outside uh where's
the sheep Let Me
In it's Amanda run for your
[Music]
lives JJ over
here she's
coming do you know where the story
that's right you
fools okay thanks bye ah what a boring
meeting do you know where the store is
do you know
where what the oh my gosh she just got
hit by a
truck don't forget to
subscribe why didn't you invite me to
the Obby because you suck at obies you
always always hold us back hey I thought
I was good well stop thinking that
because it's
[Music]
fall sorry Pablo that was meant for
Bobby okay kids today we will be Turing
another
daycare I heard it's really pretty like
ours pack your belongings as I get the
school
[Applause]
bus
they're
here welcome guys thanks for coming be
free to check out all our
amenities guys I'm having such a great
time in here this is so much better than
our daycare I agree on
[Music]
three okay kid story time once upon a
time there was a shrimp who didn't get
eaten by a shark because he was
subscribed to the crystalline Gamers is
that Janice yeah I think so Janice
Janice is that you what Masha JJ what
are you guys doing here we came here to
check out your cool daycare uh don't
mess with me unless I'll kick you Janice
did you say something sweetie um no mom
I'm just happy to see the visitors great
anyways it's playtime why did you gather
all of us here B
well it seems like Janice is being nice
to us because her mom's the teacher
let's take advantage of her
I hey Janet can you help me carry this
robot since you're so jacked huh
okay thanks
Janice hey Janice can I read your book
but you have your own book though but I
want to read
yours
Bobby yeah here you can have my book
Bobby oh wow how kind of you
Janice oh no my bear got stuck up there
Janice Janice Janice please please come
help me my bear got stuck on the roof
fine I'll go get
it I got it I'm coming down
now here Masha this is it right yes yes
thank you thank you okay everyone Time
For Recess guys I feel bad let's be nice
to JIS and invite her to play no yeah
let's invite her come on
[Applause]
JJ hey Janice we were wondering if you
wanted to come and play with
[Music]
us don't do it Janice
no oh my gosh are you okay J ha my mom
isn't here now now I'm going to get all
of you
guys what happened
Mommy Janice come with me
please I also ate turkey for breakfast
interesting hi everybody today's my
birthday happy birthday Masha happy
birthday she's lying is not her birthday
yes it is you don't know anything look
these are my invitations cool am I
invited of course you are and JJ Zoe and
Pablo there's going to be a clown I bet
the party's going to be lame that's okay
you're not invited
anyways whatever he just kidding B baby
you can come huh oh well DJ your mom is
here let's go JJ
come on JJ you're going to be late to
your friend's birthday
party who is
that hi Bobby hi JJ's mom can I get a
ride please sure
Bobby D Masha why wouldn't she invite me
who does she think she is I have to find
a way to get into the
party
[Music]
H grandma get the
door hi hey guys come on
in hey
guys they're having
fun the clown is here I'll have a few
words with him hey mister hey
can I talk to you please sure hop
[Music]
in
oops the clown is here
hey come on
in hey kids ready to have fun
hold on a second why is the clown so
small this clown is sus I'm just short
now who wants a
balloon there you go one for you and one
for you can I have one no but it's my
birthday how come I don't have one look
at his headside he look a lot like boss
baby you're right why did you do that
where's my clown because I wasn't
invited you ruin the
[Music]
party but I did invite you no you didn't
I didn't hear you whatever where's my
clown in the pool I don't have a pool
whatever in the
M let's get him
out sorry
[Music]
Masha yeah and I told my cat not to do
it anymore but he keep doing
it hey kids today someone new will be
joining us so make sure you be nice to
her okay cool another girl yay I hope
she likes
business I hope she likes the
[Music]
troll I hope she likes
animals
yeah me too bye
[Music]
mommy
huh um ma'am the high school is across
the street be quiet and get away from my
face you don't have to tell me twice
everybody this is Janice she looks like
she's going lifting weights what did you
say chill man I mean woman I didn't say
anything you better not you big head
she's a little mean yeah I agree with
you it's playtime and after we will eat
our snacks
yay give me
that
loser have you beaten level 24 yet I
love my monkey I love my monkey I love
my monkey so very much hi Janice give me
that that
hey I'll take
[Music]
this okay kids it's snack
time give me your cookie but that's mine
I don't
care give me that no give me that you
big head no here just take mine I don't
want it
I'll be back for your
lunch we'll see about that it's recess
time I'm here to call a meeting about
the mean girl yeah she took my monkey
she took my cookie yeah she yelled at me
yeah and she made fun of my head well
your head is kind of big boss
baby anyways this is what we're going to
do hey Big Head come give me a push who
who me yes
you push me don't mind if I
[Applause]
[Music]
do bye JJ have a nice day and daycare I
wait JJ you forgot to give me back my
phone thank you bye-bye
guys I have something cool in my
backpack let me see it well okay kids
settle down it's Story
Time and the froggy said I'm not a
princess I'm a donut so please subscribe
to the crystalline
Gamers and like the video too said
froggy Masha let me see what you brought
not yet the teacher is still here here
the teacher's always going to be here so
let me see it no d n okay kids Excuse me
while I go to the
bathroom Masha this is your chance yeah
Masha show us what you brought okay fine
this is my
phone you're not supposed to bring that
to
dayare yeah you can get in trouble leave
me alone everybody and my your own be
swag okay kids I'm back now we're going
[Music]
to what was
that she did it no it wasn't me she's
lying no I'm
not oh um Masha meet me by my desk
hm you're not supposed to bring your
phone to daycare I'm calling your
parents to pick it up but teacher
[Music]
teacher Masha I don't want to hear
it so you want to
huh when did you get so
tall O
A
Bear hi Masha Masha get away from that
bear no This Is My Friend Bear he's
friendly
[Music]
hello she's back Who's Back
Janice oh no not again
e did you guys subscribe are you talking
about the crystal Gamers yeah I did
that's
[Music]
good I love this phone I'm going to keep
it let me make a phone call where's my
phone has anybody seen my phone Masha
did it what no I didn't I may have left
it at
[Music]
home
okay kids we're having lunch soon yay
finally who did that boss baby did it I
saw what no she did that's enough go to
time
out I don't like
[Music]
Jenice there you
go what happened to my hair teacher I
know who did it Zoe did it what Zoe no
it wasn't me that's it time out
Zoe Zoe it's okay I believe
you perfect caught you this time teacher
teacher I got footed got what Jen's
pushing your car in the water what my
car let me
see home Dennis come
here you've been caught but it wasn't me
you were caught on the phone you have
detention oh
[Applause]
[Music]
man everyone come in for story
time and the cow said I'm not a cow I'm
a burger so please please please please
please please please please please
please please please subscribe to the
crystalline Gamers and like the video
DN okay kids I will see you tomorrow and
don't forget tomorrow's costume day make
sure to come with your best outfit and
the winner gets a prize I can't wait for
tomorrow I'm going to be a clown I'm
going to be a warrior what are you going
to be Bobby I'm going to be a banana
okay bye see you guys tomorrow see you
later ah I can't find my banana suit
what am I going to do I reflect on my
reflection and I ask myself the question
I'm going to be a
warrior I have an idea I have to win so
I'm just going to copy boss
baby morning Bobby hey
everyone hey you're wearing the same
costume as me yeah doesn't it look great
on me you come copi me no it's not
exactly the same it didn't come with a
big head take it off I'm trying to win
the prize uh I don't think
so ow hey hey fight fight fight fight
fight fight fighting is not
allowed qu no
you why are you fighting barie copied my
costume no I did
not hey all your outfits look great
everyone is getting a
prize come to the front and show us your
outfit me
[Music]
first come on Boss baby
okay hey what' you do that for that's
for stealing my
outfit did you hear about the aliens
that's coming to abduct us huh what
aliens the ones coming
[Music]
tonight good morning kids today we will
be watching the crystalline Gamers
enjoy hello Jim I will be showing you
how to get I know the crystaline gamers
really yeah I play with them sometimes
isn't that right Pap and
JJ that's not true what do you mean how
do you know them then I met them in an
Obby can you bring them here tomorrow
hey I know them too really boss baby why
didn't you say so but you don't even
know the crystaline gamers yes I do
you're lying bring them then fine I will
good and I'll bring mine teacher teacher
can boss baby bring the crystalline
Gamers here tomorrow the crystalline
Gamers I love them sure they can come
the teacher said you can bring
[Applause]
them hey Crystal I was wondering if you
and emerald can stop on my daycare
tomorrow great thanks be there by 10
Shar see you
then I need to find these YouTubers but
where can I find them I need to bring
somebody tomorrow but who
H yeah hello hello great can you come
10:00 a.m. sharp
thanks H when does my friends get
here oh hey boss baby I hope you brought
your friends The crystaline
Gamers I did for your
information they're
here
hey the crystalline Gamers hey boss baby
how you doing those aren't the real
crystaline Gamers H I'm confused which
one is the real one only the real
crystaline Gamers can answer these two
questions what's your favorite color
green and blue aquamine and Par wrinkle
H okay last question how many
subscribers do you guys have
93,000
867,000 now let me check the internet
according to my phone these are the real
crystaline Gamers we were lied to um I
can explain imposters get
that wait for me yeah I know right uhhuh
where's the
[Music]
teacher
me too hi kids sorry I'm late that's
okay it's really hot in here teacher can
we go outside to the swimming pool yeah
can we go yeah sure why not they'll get
ready and meet me
outside this is much better yeah I agree
that's
fun catch
Bobby watch
out
what was
that guys we forgot the teacher I'll go
get her I'll come along
tooo I think I got her uh that's not the
teacher yeah but she couldn't have just
disappeared so I think it's the teacher
let's bring her in well here she is
that's the teacher why is she crying
because she's a baby what do we
do stop crying Masha give her your
monkey no it's mine give it to her now
or she'll never stop crying
fine no she's going to rip
it she's probably just hungry JJ try
giving her your bottle
come on JJ do it
[Applause]
now wow she's Super Hyper I can read her
a story maybe she'll fall asleep yeah go
ahead
Masha and he subscribed and liked the
video the end nice story Masha thank you
Bobby oh I just realized the book was
upside down hey look she's asleep well
I'm hungry is it snack time yeah but the
teacher's the only one who can open the
cabinets wait the cabinets are locked
now yeah ever since you started stealing
from them oh
[Music]
yeah what the what's going
on
oh no the lights went out oh no it's
flooding that's a lot of water yeah it
is what are we going to do I want my
mommy look she's big again teacher wake
up I don't like this teacher wake up hey
hello you got to wake up what huh what
in the world am I doing in the
[Applause]
crib
hi hey Bobby come this
way listen up everyone this is our new
student Bobby Bobby would you like to
introduce yourself hello I'm Bobby I'm
JJ's new neighbor nice to meet you
Bobby my favorite thing to do is troll
you're a troll no I don't mean that I
mean I like tricks and
pranks that sounds awesome here's my
business card call me um okay okay kids
today we're going on another field trip
oh cool where are we going we're going
to tour the Space Center also we'll be
taking a space bus
there this is very exciting oh look it's
here come on guys let's
go
we're here okay kids we're about to go
inside but before we do we have to gear
up okay now that we're geared up let's
head inside but remember don't patch
anything can't make any promises this is
the lunchroom I'm hungry me too let's
see what they got in
[Music]
here ice cream
candy I like this
place this is the medical room hey look
I'm
sleeping up
here is the crystal orb this is a secret
power source for the ship so shiny I
want to touch it chill man and lastly
the control room okay kids I have to use
the bathroom I'll be right back and
don't touch anything wow this is
great countdown I wonder what this
button
[Music]
does oh no Bobby you launched the rocket
ship oops sorry my bad sorry won't get
us back to Earth what are we going to do
um LIF off start in pus 10 seconds
teacher Bobby sent us to space 8 7 I'm
really sorry oh this is all just a
stimulation it's not real 2
1 we have
ignition
pH let's all get snacks eh I'm not that
hungry
[Music]
ma'am you just run a red light and
you're going to fast I'm going to give
you a ticket but officer I can explain
you're being find 1 million robu but
have a nice day ah ah a
man man I'm so mad yeah every time when
I clap my hands it's a sounds like this
yeah it was the craziest dream good
morning teacher go sit
down why is the teacher being so mean
what not our teacher she's super nice
everyone be quiet grab a book and read
it
quietly I think the teacher woke up on
the wrong side of the bed this morning
see I told you she even greet me this
morning you probably did something wrong
she's always nice to me watch this hey
teacher I like your outfit today you're
supposed to be reading with the others
jeez yikes you're right Bobby I think
something is wrong with the teacher I
said
[Music]
read how long is it going to take we've
been reading forever it's recess time
yeah who's going to tell the teacher
it's recess
time Masa I think you should go tell the
teacher why me why not you no way man
I'm too scared let's play Rock Paper
Scissors okay Rock Paper Scissors Shoot
Ro I guess we all did paper Pablo you
go oh
yeah go sit down
Pablo okay well I have to go wee we uh
teacher I have to wee we so can I go to
the bathroom please I don't know can you
it's an emergency can you um well can I
can you can I I don't know uh you know
what never mind I don't have to go
[Music]
anymore Susie are you okay I think I
broke my rib again all right kids it's
story time once upon a time a teacher
got a ticket she was so upset the whole
day because she had to pay 1 million
Robo the only way to make the teacher
happy was to subscribe to The crystaline
Gamers what the is that what happened to
you today teach yeah I'm sorry guys we
can help you pay for the ticket yeah we
can have a lemonade stand and we'll make
1 million r Robux for it thanks guys
then come on what are we waiting for
let's go lemonade lemonade lemonade
lemonade only 1 million Robux huh what's
this hi ma'am would you like some
lemonade to help us raise some money oh
I'm still thirsty just what I needed
I'll take
one huh what this tastes disgusting
what' you put in it crayons
ew Masha really crayons I thought it
would give it
color ma'am there seems to be a mistake
what do you mean I meant to charge you
10 robu not a million oh I have that
easy thank you I apologize for the
inconvenience so that's all it seems so
what a waste of time I'll take
that huh hey boss baby give that back JJ
today's halloween go upstairs and wear
your costume you're going to wear for
[Applause]
daycare cocon JJ you said your first
words get in the car so I can drop you
off to
daycare bye
JJ I like your costume JJ C
I like you guys outfit who are you guys
supposed to be for Halloween I obviously
have the best costume I'm Mickey Mouse
I'm
Sonic I'm a witch princess
cocon I'm a minion I'm ladybug who could
tell what my outfit is o o me are you
Peppa Pig no are you Patrick naha you
look like the lady who kidnapped JJ and
I yeah yes I'm Mommy Long Legs okay kids
it's time to go trick or treating get
your candy bags
okay trick or treat you guys look so
cute one for you and one for you take
some more have fun thank
you trick or treat smell my feet give me
something good to eat well howy NN I
sure can you can get one you can get one
and you can get one what did you say
kidss I want more no boss baby be nice
have a howdy Halloween okay kids it's
time to go back to the daycare can we do
one more please yeah my bag is not even
full fine don't get lost
yay trick or treat trick or treat trick
or treat thanks trick or treat trick or
[Music]
treat
give me gy come on Pao let's
go I got so much candy I got Skittles
Reese's and Twizzlers I got a toothbrush
like the last time if you haven't seen
that video go ahead and check it out I
got bubblegum Bubba what did you get hey
what point wait Pablo you can talk I
look Pablo wait who are
you teacher teacher this isn't Pablo
what Pablo is missing
uhhuh oh no you're not
Pablo let's get you home and find
[Music]
Pablo bye
Andre
Pablo where are you
look yay Pablo we found
you sorry I got the wrong problem okay
kids now let's go eat some candy
[Music]
y everybody get ready for a play
rehearsal in the school across the
street ooh ooh what play are we doing
The Three Little Pigs yay YY I'm so
excited for this play yeah I can't wait
this play is going to be dumb M I don't
know it might be
fun come on everybody let's go follow me
here are your characters boss baby as
the wolf Zoe JJ and Pablo as pigs and Ma
and Bobby as villagers everyone start
rehearsing I will wolf and wolf and blow
your house
down that's not where we are yeah and
those aren't even the right words I know
but that's my favorite
part ah this is boring just read your
lines
bro fine little pig little pig let me in
more emphasis boss baby ah little pig
little pig let me in then I'll cook you
for dinner okay that's enough go home
and practice your lines finally little
pig little pig let me in practice in is
boring I'll do it later let me go play
some
games oh why is this girl right behind
me get your own lane I'm trying to get
first
place oh my gosh it's night time let me
start practicing little pig little pig
let me
[Music]
in you guys look perfect
we will be on in 5 minutes where is boss
baby I'm here what happened to your
costume oh it got shred on the way here
you look terrible the play is about to
start don't worry I've been practicing
all night yeah you better not mess it up
for us yeah boss baby your wolf head is
in the back okay okay kids
[Music]
Showtime good evening everyone today
we'll be doing The Three Little
Pigs little pig little pig let me in
your house will not withstand my mega
fart that's not you're lying bu baby
I'll tear down this house with my
claw not by the hair of my chinny chin
chin but you have no hair on your chin
boss baby you're messing up the plate
yeah this is complete nonsense I have to
stop the play it's not going
well I'll pull the fire alarm
what is that
sound everybody this is a fire drill
we'll finish the play tomorrow come
on everybody go get your costumes we are
finishing the play today so what
happened yesterday I did it it was me I
pulled the fire alarm what why because
you were messing up the show I hope you
practiced last night yeah I did come on
guys good evening everyone the play will
start
again little pig little pig let me in
not by the hairs on my chinny chin chins
then I'll HFF and puff and blow your
house
down o o little pig little pig let me in
not by the hairs on our chinny chin
chant then I'll huff and I'll puff and
I'll blow your house
down this time I'll get
them little pig little pig let me in not
by the hairs of our chinny chin chin
then I'll hop then I'll pop and I'll
blow this house
[Music]
down ah I'm tired why isn't this house
going away I can answer that cuz it's
made of of brick and I'm here to chase
you away uh-oh come back here come back
here and they all lived happily ever
after don't forget to like And subscribe
everybody thanks for watching bye now
turkeys can't fly yeah they can I can't
wait for Thanksgiving yeah Susie me too
yeah and all the money that we get from
it you don't get money on Thanksgiving
I'm at all the food Pablo good
morning hi Pablo we're so excited for
your play date yeah I can't wait either
you're not invited boss baby why not
because you didn't invite me to your
play date uh yeah but I invited Pablo to
it Pablo is boss baby invited oh yeah
thank you Pablo am I invited too
oh sorry I can't come I have Sports
practice thanks for the invite though
okay kids it's story time Once Upon a
Time the turkey survive because it's
subscribe to the crystalline
Gamers that's enough Masher please get
the door
sweetie hi
pabloo
Pablo hola you must be Pablo friends
come on in and have fun cookie on the
table Yeah cookies what huh where are
all the
[Music]
cookies what is it
Pablo Pablo is this your little
sister she's so cute who are you calling
cute I mean gooo gaka no we just heard
you talk okay you got me what are you
guys doing in my Big Brother's house we
just came for a play dat what's a play
lady when you invite your friends over
and play okay can I play too uh sure
you're so cute can I hold you yeah psch
you can't get me come on guys let's just
go play yeah let's just go outside pass
it to me over here I'm open I'm open
pass it to me okay you
ready wow she's really good pass it to
me
P I got the ball hey hey get it
[Music]
back give me the ball Maria hey where
are you guys going yeah come
back turn around Maria Maria come back
let's do something else yeah I agree
let's go
dance
bro
what
e let's play hide and seek yeah maybe
that would be fun Pablo you
count
oh where is
everybody they're playing hide and seek
Pablo Pablo JJ's over there in the
crib and the girl is behind the plane
[Music]
man oh man oh Pablo I found another one
what that's cheating I can get the candy
girl for you hey what are you
doing you're not cute
anymore ha I found you baly no fair this
is not fun yeah your sister's ruining
everything we're
[Music]
leaving yeah good
leave
okay Maria it's time for bed now now now
now good finally we can play
[Music]
yay yeah and then I picked up the turtle
and it farted that's so disgusting yeah
that's what happen it was really
gross oh no it's Janice
[Music]
hi hi teach teacher hi Janice make sure
you're kind to the rest of the class yes
Ma'am why are you guys hiding be quiet
and hide why what for and who's that
lady over there that's not a lady that's
Janice is she new no she's the mean girl
you don't want to mess with her what did
she do well a lot get away from my face
you big head give me
that give me that I'll take
this give me your
cookie
no that doesn't sound very nice maybe
she's nice now is she
coming hi my name is Susie and I like
chips nice to meet you okay who cares ew
what's that ugly thing on your face oh I
got into a fight with Masha last week go
check that video out if you haven't seen
it already oh okay so you have potential
let me see what
hi Pablo thanks for giving me your
airplane that's not nice Janice why are
you making cry H it's
[Music]
funny
teacher teacher not now guys I'm on the
phone anybody else oh no uh-uh not me
good that's what I
thought hey you peanut head over here
who me yes you with the green shirt yes
you Dum Dum oh come over
here get me something to drink yes your
highness lunchtime yes and after that we
escaped B's Academy that's so cool it
was an awesome game she's coming guys oh
no get up and fan me no touch me if you
[Music]
can are you okay yes I'm fine Hi how are
you Boss baby wait you're not going to
beat me up no of course not why would I
okay yeah I was a big
booger hi beautiful p people what
happened to her don't worry about it I
took care of
her what does that even mean hey guys
have you noticed boss baby being mean
ever since Janice turned nice yeah he's
been bossing everyone around especially
Janice I hate to say it but I think
Janice was better when she was the mean
one fan harder Janice I'm hot you stin
at this I'm
[Music]
sorry
we have to help Janice something is
wrong Janice come over
here huh me Masha okay I'm coming
up wao what happened well you see what
are you guys looking at what do you guys
want um never mind I think she's
back hey big head get out of my Throne
yes your
highness everyone give me 10 jumping
jacks while I subscribe to the land
Gamers a I hate jumping jack make sure
you like the video and comment the word
Janice Here We Go
Again Birthday Bobby oh yeah it's my
birthday oh
yeah hello ma'am hi how can I help you
can I talk to you in private yeah sure
well you see yeah yeah yeah it's my
birthday oh really and that's why
Bobby can I see you please guys I'll be
right
back hi Bobby hi I am here to inform you
that you have come of age huh what does
come of age mean now that you are older
you can't be in daycare anymore what do
you mean it means you have been promoted
to kindergarten okay cool I'll inform
your Aunt Karen that you start tomorrow
okay
cool Bobby what did the teacher say to
you since today is my birthday I'm now
going to conect Garten wow does that
mean you get to drive a car no s I get
to take the bus to school oh we're going
to miss you Bobby I'm going to miss you
guys too no I'm going to be stuck with
these losers no boss baby you're the
loser anyways have fun in kindergarten
bye
guys I can't wait for kindergarten this
day is going to be so much
fun huh is that the bus
oh no the bus is
here wait wait for me slow down wait for
me wait wait for
me jeez I'm out of
breath hi Bobby hi hi class this is our
new student Bobby please introduce
yourself hi I'm Bobby and I like to
troll nobody cares sit down
okay Bobby please take your
seat okay class can anyone tell me 2+ 2
oh I know I me H Bobby H five no he got
it wrong the answer is four yes good job
Aiden nice thanks Andreas uh okay this
class stinks maybe the next class will
be better all right class it's time for
PE are you guys
ready
why is everyone on the other team
go nice job you
[Music]
want and then it got eaten by a
crocodile oh my goodness that's so funny
c c can I sit here no going throw toys
go said somewhere else nice one
Andreas I'm not in enjoying this I guess
being older is hard I miss my
daycare and this F's
disgusting what I didn't even get a
chance to
eat hey that's my seat so what are you
going to do about it
whatever all right everybody it's time
to take your test now what I'm not
prepared yet and
begin I can't do it
may I help you sir we made a mistake we
got the wrong Bobby we meant Bobby fit
I'll take him back to daycare Bobby
please follow this gentleman out the
door perfect
[Music]
timing I wonder what Bobby's doing Bobby
hi guys kindergart is over already
apparently they got the wrong Bobby how
was it Bobby it was great I was so
popular everyone wanted to be my friend
I was the smartest person in all my
classes cool glad you're back yeah me
[Music]
too hi can I help
you don't you dare I know
away let me get
ready the kids will be ready
minutes bye JJ's
mom hi guys where's the
teacher that's a good question we were
wondering this same thing we're not sure
though maybe she's inside the
bathroom good morning
everyone my name is Jeff bigy I'm your
substitute today
oh um why are you singing okay everyone
said over
[Music]
Story Once Upon a Time a to got her
mouth D so subscribe to the Crystal G do
you by any chance know Miss Piggy yes
she's my wife yep I knew it we're in
trouble guys I think he's here for
Revenge okay kids why don't you go
[Music]
[Applause]
out I'll be right back Zoe I have to use
the restroom okay
ew it stinks let me go to the one
[Music]
upstairs what the teacher teacher what
in the world are you doing here lower
your voice the sub kidnapped me help me
why didn't you just get up and leave my
legs and hands are tied don't worry
teacher we'll help
you everyone come over here guess what
[Music]
don't worry Pablo we'll get to the
bottom of this let's call the police
yeah Masha use your phone I didn't bring
my phone today what the one time you
didn't bring your
phone listen up this is what we
do got it
C come on
inside hey Mr Piggy you must be hungry
not falling for the sh a man come on it
worked last
time oh I'm sorry guys he didn't fall
for it let's jump him I'll get him from
the back yes
[Music]
Zoe give us your phone number
no I'm calling the
police yeah dude you're coming with
me let's go get the teacher teacher
teacher we saved you thank you
kids I can't wait till Christmas me to
it's going to be great this year Sophia
tell Mama I want a PS5 no you tell her
hello okay okay it's closed okay thank
you Maria your daycare is closed today
can I get a Pablo's daycare M okay as
long as you behave yourself
yay bye Mama adios
chiao come on Pablo let's go to
theare
[Music]
hello can you drop my da off here her
day care is close
today oh sure no problem what she doing
here apparently she's here because her
daycare is closed yeah okay just behave
yourself this time I
will hi Maria hi Lucy what's that
scrumptious snack you're eating these
are my favorite snacks Doritos wow they
look so yummy I wish I had
some hi boor baby that's a lot of money
it's boss baby and I have $3 wow you're
rich yeah and I like your Hippo Too
TJ hi Tasha and Chloe hi Maria what's
that shiny thing I won an award at a
talent show oh my goodness that's so
cool Maria look this is my favor
favorite toy it's so cute yeah he's my
monkey he's very strong I bet he is not
for
long what's your reading Egghead now
that's just rude just my favorite book
about trolling you better not troll me H
that book would be really useful okay
kids it's nap
[Music]
[Applause]
time
I'm bored let's cause some
trouble I'll take this I'll take this oh
now the
teacher now nobody will find their thing
huh I thought I heard something e that
was
close wakey wakey wow that was a good
nap yeah I feel really
refreshed all right kid it's playtime
you can go get your things in the
cabinet wait a minute I can't find my
trophy guys hey I can't find my chip
yeah I can't find my book where's my
monkey and my
money nobody can find any of their
things I can be a detective I can find
out who took all of your stuff yeah you
can do that for us how nice of you to
help us area all right let's get started
boy baby it's boss baby what were you
doing during nap time uh I was sleeping
guilty guilty guilty guilty guys boy
baby stole all your stuff huh what no I
didn't why would I steal my own money
you probably wanted to sell all our
stuff on eBay what yeah I didn't do it
I I didn't do it I didn't do it I didn't
do it everyone stop boss baby stole all
our stuff is that so it wasn't me let me
go check the cameras
uhoh it was Maria Maria you did a bad
thing I'm really sorry I'm calling your
mom no
no hey kids today's career day we are
going on a field trip to to visit
different jobs what's career day it's
when you get to see other people's jobs
oh okay oh I already know what I want to
be when I grow up I want to be a vet
that's boring you should be a clown no
you're a clown that's not even a job I
want to be a lawyer so I can put boss
baby in
jail yeah I want to be a policeman so I
can arrest boss baby too why is everyone
ganging up on me because you always Rin
everything I do not yes you do like all
the time roll the
flashback o
cake now go get him
tiger what's this oh cool it's an
airplane I'll just use this for my show
and
tell why did you do that where's my
clown because I wasn't invited uh that's
what she said she said she likes Bobby
no I never said that those were all
accidents anyways I want to be a baker
so I can make
[Music]
chips yeah that will be the perfect
job awesome JJ that's a cool one okay
guys let's go first step the fire
station
y hi guys my name is Rob I work here as
a firefighter my job is to save lives
and this is my fire truck it helps me
get the job done who wants to sit in the
truck me me me you with the big head
yes wo cool what does this pedal
[Music]
do he crashed the truck oh my gosh what
am I going to do I'm
okay hi kids my name is Miss Beth hi
Miss be and I make cookies pie bread
donuts and do you make chips yes do you
want to make some with me yes okay let's
all make
[Music]
some I love flour so you want to do this
and this and I'll go put it in the oven
Yum Cake is my favorite it's taking too
long let me increase the
heat yeah that's much better I like
this what's that smell oh know it's
burning the cheeks are burning the
cheeks are burning everybody up wait
what you ruined my chck sorry guys how
about we go to the police station next
okay hi officer Eric I protect the
streets from the bad guys cool make sure
you guys don't touch anything wa I
wonder what this button does
I'm
free
uh-oh what have you done I I didn't mean
to what do we do don't worry kids we
will get the criminal we just need our
Donuts from the bakery didn't you hear
the bakery burned down because the fire
truck got crashed who's responsible for
that BOS baby been ruining everything so
far um sorry get in
there wait no please I'm sorry I didn't
mean
to okay you're done now get out what I'm
done it was just a prank just to teach
you a lesson yeah boss baby stop
touching things without permission
gotcha not cool dude hey kids we have a
new kid hi my name is Susie and I like
chips nice to meet you sometimes I grow
and Shrink but I'll tell you that story
later hi Susie nice to meet you Susie
what's your favorite chips well there's
Cheetos and Doritos I like them all do
you like money and yes I like money
because it buys me chip I know that's
right okay guys have fun with Susie hi
guys what are you guys
doing talking in where's that smell
coming from probably Pablo and JJ
diapers nah they would have told the
teacher if so we should probably find
where the smell is coming from but I
don't smell anything JJ is your diaper
full I thought I smelled something hey
Bobby get over here what do you need are
you guys smelling something disgusting
you smell that too yeah smells like a
dead animal see you or it might be the
smell from the bathroom I don't think so
because the smell is constant it's not
going away like it should I need to ask
the teachers for chips I'll be right
back this is weird we never had a
problem like this in daycare wait do you
guys smell that no exactly the smell
disappeared you're right Bobby how
strange oh well maybe it was just a
trash are aliens real that's silly Bobby
they don't
exist hi guys look I got
Doritos oh my gosh it
[Music]
stinks hey you want to train
lunches
[Music]
what's wrong with him the smell must be
Pablo he's probably feeling guilty let's
go inside and see what's up with Pablo
teacher teacher did Pablo come in here
where's Pablo Pablo went homesick a o
bummer what
going why they leave um hey hello did
you you guys hear that it sounds like it
came from su's behind I know right now
we know where the smell is coming from
we should have known all along now we
need to stay away from her I feel bad
for the girl it's not even a prank she
smells so bad yeah and she's really nice
too I mean everyone farts too we could
go over to her don't be stubborn JJ
let's go I guess so I got an
idea hi hi guys hey hi sorry you ran
away earlier you can come play with us
oh that's okay I was just eating my
snacks come on everyone let's go
upstairs and
play JJ it's time for
daycare oh yeah today is picture day I
bought you a new outfit go up and try it
[Music]
on
it fits perfectly let's
go see you
later good morning kiddos you guys look
all great
today we'll go take our pictures in an
hour let me go ahead and call the
photographer who are you that's JJ silly
I like your outfit thanks not not
[Music]
you okay guys it's time to go outside
and make sure not to get your clothes
[Music]
dirty oh
no Pablo are you okay oh no your clothes
is dirty let's go tell the
teacher you have to tell
her sorry Pablo teacher teacher Pablo
got his clothes dirty is that
so I can fix that Pablo come with
[Music]
me all
clean let's go take our
pictures I'm here come on guys let's go
take our pictures Pablo you can go first
say
[Music]
cheese finally my
turn wait let me redo that
next now a group photo everyone say
cheese
[Music]
cheese hi I know right JJ yeah this
comic book is really funny look at this
good morning everyone as you know today
is Field Day teacher what's field day
field day is a day where you guys will
compete against each other to win a
trophy here it is wow we will be
adventuring to the high school soccer
field after Story Time that trophy is
going to be mine in the meanwhile why
don't you guys go play well I go on the
computer and pair y'all up
I hope I get a good partner me too cuz I
want my trophy okay kids it's story time
you can check your partners afterwards
yay I hope I'm partner with you Zoe me
too H I wonder who my partner is and
Humpty dummy was fixed because he
subscribed to the crystalline Gamers I
hope it's Bobby he's really good at
games I'll go
check
let me see who I'm paired
with masha's with Pablo and a Bobby's
with JJ who am I
with what Zoe no I don't want to be with
a girl girls aren't good at
sports oh I know I'll just switch it
around I'll make Bobby my partner and
then we'll
win and then he liked the video the end
okay kids go check your partner on the
computer Pablo you're with Masha yay and
JJ I'm with
you I guess I'm with you boss baby all
right hooray we're going to win yeah
okay kids let's go to the soccer field
and change our
outfits okay kids we will be doing three
different activities piggyback race sack
race and wagon race first one is
piggyback race first to cross the finish
line wins
easy on your mark get set
go oh
man
good job Zoe and
JJ wow so we won don't worry B bab we'll
win next
time okay kids the next game is potato
hop I'm ready good luck boss baby thanks
but I don't need it Ready Set
Go
[Music]
what
the yay I win I win Yay good job Masha
and Pablo you win this round good job
Masha thanks Zoe what happened we almost
won I was being chased by bees we're
losing maybe I should have stuck with
Zoe okay this is the last race pull your
partner on a wagon to the Finish Line
Ready set
[Applause]
go hurry up man I'm going I'm
going congratulations Zoe and JJ you
win here you go y you made us lose it
was your big head you're too heavy I
shouldn't have changed my partner what
Bas you changed your partner you cheated
shame on you yeah that's what you get
cheaters never
Prosper good job Zoe oh yeah and you too
JJ Kids we are going on a camp camping
trip everybody go get your camping
[Applause]
gear it's time to go everybody get on
the bus okay I can't
[Music]
wait we're here why is your backpack so
big cuz I have bug spray books and my
Barbie collection sheesh everybody pick
a partner and set up your your tents Hey
Zoe do you want to be my partner yeah JJ
do you want to be my partner I ask first
no I did
Super he's my neighbor I've known him
longer I asked first no I did I did no I
[Music]
did okay great everybody seems to be
partnered up Masha and Zoe Pablo and JJ
boss baby and Bobby what everybody set
up your
[Music]
tents that's not how you do it you're
doing it wrong no I'm not I'm following
the instructions forget the instructions
okay kids first activity to do is
fishing this is boring there's no fish
in here this stinks let's go over to the
boat good idea Zoe
yeah wow oh wow Pizza this is really
delicious what the hey what are you guys
doing on my yach get out of
here oh no we're lost what was that
noise calm down everybody I speak fair
then say
something
everybody
run this way everyone I see the
tent finally we're
[Applause]
[Music]
back hey guys look at my new shirt
that's cool Bobby where did you get it I
got it from the crystaline gamer
store hey JJ Pablo I want to show you
guys
something I want to show you a magic
trick show me your
palm here hold
this Pablo now you hold
this I will now count from 1 to 10 1 2 3
4 5 five baby what are you doing to them
nothing mind your own business go and
play with your dolls tell me what you're
doing it's magic now go away what kind
of magic voodoo go away no I
won't guys come and see the magic boss
baby is doing oh
no what are you doing boss baby nothing
he won't tell me JJ what are you two
doing
boss baby what did you do to them why
are they crying I did nothing I don't
know why they're
crying I think their hands are glued to
the toy oh no they can't open their
hands teacher teacher come
quickly what's going on here boss baby
glued JJ in Pablo's hands to a toy boss
baby is that
true I'm sorry I didn't know it would
hurt them so you glued the hippo to
their hands let me call the
doctor hello
[Music]
doctor it's okay guys I'll get the hippo
off your hands there you go and you too
there all done thank you Doctor goodbye
goodbye no more playing with harmful
substance yes teacher I'm sorry all
right everyone come to together it's
Story
Time Masha I put Donuts in your lunch
bag for you to take to dayer thanks
Grandma let's go Grandma wait for
me bye Grandma hi
guys why do you look so happy today yeah
you look happy do you want to prank the
teacher I can help you I'm planning on
it right now I'm not pranking anyone I
have donuts for lunch I'd sure like to
have one right now don't eat my Donuts
I'll be sad how much do you want for
them they're not for sale but I can
share them with you when it's time to
eat you got yourself a deal that's not a
Burg boss baby yes boss baby I'm being
kind so you say thank you yeah
sure teacher Pablo is
crying Pablo why are you crying
I think he's hungry you're just saying
that cuz you already want to eat your
Donuts Pablo are you
hungry okay Pablo we can eat lunch in 10
[Music]
minutes I need some fresh air I'll be
right
back H Ooh La
La it's my lucky day oh why is Bobby by
the the lunch cabinet the
donut Pablo you can eat your lunch now
how about the rest of us can we eat too
yes everyone can
eat oh no what's the matter what did you
see a cockroach in your bag or something
I think her donut is missing yes my
Donuts is missing how did you know did
you take them no I did not don't be sad
Masha we will help you look for it let's
go oh
[Music]
okay I don't see it it's not
here it's okay Masha we'll find them
Bobby aren't you going to tell Masha
that you stole her donut what are you
talking
about what Bobby I can't believe you
took my donut for baby's sake I didn't
take your
Donuts teacher
teacher Bobby took my donut but I saw
you by the cabinet I didn't take it
we're not playing with you Bobby give it
back Bobby did you take mases Donuts I
did not I just wanted to see what an
Karen got me for lunch everyone get
him you can run but you can't hide sorry
Masha I forgot to pack you your Donuts I
have them here and I also have donuts
for
everyone I'm sorry guys and especially
you Bobby that's fine Masha I'll get
boss baby next
time yum like And subscribe for a donut
this is so good thanks
grandma and then I got my shoes dirty oh
wow that's too bad and then I caught it
that's a really cor hey kids we're going
on a field trip to watch the corn
kid kids practice using the word
accidentally in a sentence will I go get
the
bus can I go first go ahead yesterday I
accidentally farted in my dad's nose and
he got pink
eyes well I accidentally flushed money
down the toilet I accidentally Katty
chat my Aunt Karen in the
neck but don't worry she's fine she's
just in the hospital again my grandma
accidentally got run over by a reindeer
cool me too I accidentally ended up at
JJ's brother's party I was there too and
I accidentally ate all their chips what
you guys went to a party without me yeah
and it was really fun okay kids get on
the
bus H Zoe is my friend how come she
didn't invite me to the party
Hey Zoe do you want to sit with me on
the bus oh sorry Masha Susie already
asked me oh all right get in the back of
the line Masha
whatever okay guys come inside the
bus a ducked a lemonade
and the hey we're here hey guys let's go
get pizza
no we want
popcorn Masha what's wrong my dra
beeswax Bobby you do you I guess come on
Boss
baby for me I really like what do you
like about hey Susie can I switch SE
switches so I can sit next to Zoe no I
want to sit here I like this Masha go
sit down we can't see Masha come sit up
here with
meating
[Music]
corn it has
to it's a big
lob okay kids let's go get our Fat Juicy
Burgers
h m this is so good I know right but
corn is
better and that's the last one finally
this is my chance I guess they next to
Zoe hey get up that's my seat no I got
here first Zoe is my best friend I
should sit next to her sorry Masha she
got here first Masha you're just
overreacting calm
down car my food wow stop stealing my
best friend girls stop
fighting guys stop y'all are both my
friends but Masha you will always be my
first friend in daycare okay Zoe sorry
Susie I think I broke my red oops can we
go home
now by JJ have fun with your egg hunt
today good morning today will be Easter
egg hunting get off that
table take your buckets and meet me
outside as I take this phone
[Music]
call okay everyone here is what we're
going to do there are hidden eggs around
the playground you guys have to find
them good luck yeah yeah yeah I already
done this before really when in my old
daycare okay ready set
go yay I found found one so did I me and
Pablo found
one another
one yay yay great now my clothes are
going to get
[Music]
wet I'll take that hey that's mine not
anymore okay everybody snap
[Music]
time
guys guys look it's a
[Music]
bunny what's up
doc where's the bunny what in the
[Music]
world
run teacher there's a big scary bunny
take me there it's right here what the
don't be silly guys it's just a cute
bunny and That's all
folks what did y'all do this weekend my
monkey woke me up this morning I played
rainbow friends I almost won but I
lost oh
yeah
oh oh yeah hey kids if I call your name
come on this side Masha Bobby JJ by baby
and
[Music]
Zoe teacher teacher what's wrong as you
all know today is Pablo's birthday oh
yeah is there anything we can do for him
let's throw him a party that's a great
idea Zoe we could throw him a surprise
party
yeah let me go prepare the
cake
[Music]
all right everyone huddle
up he's here Pablo go sit
down ew that was a close one let's start
getting ready
[Music]
guys oh no Pablo go
away
pH that was
close Pablo go
[Applause]
away I can't wait for the secret B baby
it's going to be so fun pass baby this
is going to be the best pass baby behind
you huh uh Pablo what are you doing here
get out of
here
[Music]
anyways
everyone get
ready
Pablo Pablo Pablo come
downstairs
surprise happy birthday
[Music]
Pao
helicopter
helicopter what the Pablo are you
okay hurry up JJ you don't want to be
late for
daycare and don't forget your
[Music]
uniform great job JJ let's be on our way
hey guys today detective Chuck will be
coming to talk to us he's going to come
from the detection office and teach us
how to be a detective home where's JJ I
saw him still at his house but he'll be
here though I guess he'll meet us here
later teacher teacher I was a detective
before great Masha you're one step ahead
of us this is so cool I can't
wait everybody it's time for story time
once upon a time a turtle became very
fast because he subscribed to the
crystalline Gamers by
JJ morning JJ glad you decided to join
us I like your outfit JJ you look like a
real
detective hello class detective chck is
here you guys enjoy hello guys today I'm
here to teach you guys how to be
Detectives are you a real detective of
course I am how many Mysteries have you
solved I've solved 98 cases Co this is
my bad maybe one day you'll get one wo
how do you get one in order to get one
there are some things you have to do to
be qualified first you must be smart
sorry bobie you can't be a detective hey
second you can't be selfish guess you
can't be one
either and third you have to be a leader
yes uhhuh uhhuh now imagine your
detective and your teacher was missing
how would you solve the case how would
you find your
[Applause]
[Music]
teacher it wasn't
me hey you help me find my teacher I'll
pay you deal I'll take that pleasure
doing business H don't let me have to
ask you again where is my teacher um
don't make me drop your phone into this
bucket of
water have you seen my teacher um um
tell me now or I'll tell on
[Music]
you hi I'm a detective and I'm looking
for my teacher have you seen her no
sorry okay thank
you hi have you seen my teacher I
already said no
okay
[Music]
hi wow B boyage my friend whatever you
guys imagine great job thank you for
having me I'll see you guys later duty
calls that was fun
hope you kids
[Applause]
enjoyed and then I ate my mommy's snacks
JJ your mom forgot to pick me
up I like Bobby's shirt it's nice me too
oo what Zoe likes Bobby wait till
everyone else hear this all right kids
let's go
outside 51 52 Pablo come over here I
heard that Zoe likes Bobby but don't
tell
anyone see
you JJ do you want to know a
secret promise not to
tell Pablo told me that Zoe told him
that she likes Bobby shh don't tell
anyone okay kids it's time to go
home JJ your mom is here
hurry up J J Zoe Susie and Masha your
parents are here bye guys hey boss baby
what were you asking everyone outside I
wasn't telling anyone anything come on
Boss baby spill it I was telling them a
secret what was a secret I know
something you don't quit salling if you
don't tell me now then I'll pop your
balloon head off fine Zoe likes you wait
me ow yeah yes now leave me
alone Zoe likes me huh H how interesting
the next day it seems like Susie and JJ
isn't here today yeah I think so
[Music]
too good morning Zoe oh thank you Bobby
you're very welcome my sweet that was
strange oh well H why do you look goofy
I just felt a change in heart that's all
okay kids story time once upon upon a
time there was a cupid that made a woman
subscribe to the crystalline Gamers I
can't see you can take my spot Zoe okay
can you see better uh yeah H okay guys
it's snack
time I don't like my snack you can have
my cookie Zoe oh thanks Bobby no problem
my good friend it's time for
recess everybody I like to give an
announcement what's up BBY I love to
raise a toast to the girl I love most in
the whole wide world Zoe you are the
better to my toast Zoe ever since I laid
my eyes on you you've been my favorite
the smell of your hair your dotted eyes
and your red freckles Zoe will you marry
me
[Music]
um oh snap no we're just kids but I
thought you liked me who told you that
boss babies what I never said that uh
that's what she said she said she likes
Bobby no I never never said that I said
I like Bobby's shirt oops my bad well
this is
awkward bye BB and Bobby pick you up
later
[Music]
kids H I wonder what day day is up to
I'm going to go and discuss some
business
here we
[Music]
are hi
JJ JJ what happened to
[Music]
you can I help you JJ's Mom it's me
Bobby I don't think so you're not Bobby
come on JJ let's go to daycare oh man
what's going on this is just weird let
me run to daycare and and see what's up
over
there guys who are you what do you mean
who am I I'm Bobby no you're a whole
grownup yay you're not Bobby yeah I am
though prove it what is your favorite
thing to do trolling W Bobby you're as
SI as a teacher I know I need your help
we'll help you Bobby in order to be a
kid again try acting like a kid okay
what do you want me to do here play with
my toys H this is weird no you're doing
it wrong you have to sing the song I
love my gorilla I love my gorilla that's
not working try JJ's
milk here thanks
Zoe no dude it's not working what Pao
you can talk what's up so many weird
things are happening just try crawling
boy uh okay this better
work ah this isn't
working I can't take this
anymore ah I'm doomed W where did this
wind come
from look he's
moving Bobby wake
up wake
up wake up what guys your aunt is here
oh it was all a
dream hey kids welcome back are you guys
excited for
Thanksgiving most
definitely what's wrong Bobby are you
not thankful nah it's nothing all right
guys let's go outside and get some fresh
air outside
outside hey Bobby what's wrong well you
see my family won't be around this
Thanksgiving don't worry Bobby we can
celebrate Thanksgiving here in the
daycare yeah that would be great hey
kids let's head back inside all right
Bobby would you like to tell the class
what we discussed me and the teacher
created an arrangement we'll have
Thanksgiving here with all of us and
we're going to go turkey hunting yay ew
I'd rather have Thanksgiving with my
parents good riddit see you Jenice come
back that's her business Jenice get back
here Catch Me If You
Can first we're going to take the subway
to Lake
Madison it's
here now we're on our way to the turkey
patch who's driving this it's a Subway
it drives by itself right now we just
need to find a turkey look a turkey
everyone get
it come over here turkey here too B I
almost got it come over here I got it
all right guys we got the turkey see you
back at daycare where do I put the
turkey go put the turkey in the
basement huh um stay down there yeah Pao
I
agree chop chop guys we got to hurry up
this is the best Thanksgiving I can't
wait to eat the turkey me too it's my
favorite part let's talking more cooking
people calm down Bobby I'm done watching
the planks nice go start the mashed
potatoes Goldilocks okay okay Bobby go
get the turkey downstairs
okay I need to escape I'm not going to
beat anyone's
dinner
oh no the turkeyy missing
teacher teacher H I'll be right
back what are you doing Bobby what's
taking you so long the turkey is missing
oh no let's go look for it the turkey
has gone missing guys and we need
everyone's help to look for it please
don't worry we'll find it turkey turkey
turkey turkey turkey turkey where are
you turkey are you in here turkey turkey
turkey
turkey see you
losers did you guys find it no it's okay
guys Thanksgiving is about being
together you're right Bobby now let's
eat without the
turkey yay food let's go eat guys Happy
Thanksgiving everyone we are thankful
for all the crystalline Gamers
[Music]
fans
I wonder where Zoe is maybe she has some
business to attend to she's just a kid
she can't attend business deals I'm a
kid I attend business every day why do
you think I'm always wearing a suit
because baby clothes look ridiculous on
you no because I'm the boss oh yeah Zoe
always comes early but she isn't here
yet do you think she's sick maybe she's
in college now College that's not
possible I mean what would a kid be
doing in college I've been to college I
have a degree in business but I don't
think Zoe's ready for college yet I
think she can she's smart Okay kids it's
time for
recess rer can you hear me you can't T
me pass it over here over here I got it
I got it oh no the
ball what the did you guys just see
that kids it's time to go inside Zoe's
here hi everyone Hey Zoe why are you
just coming I was getting my hair done
your hair looks nice thank you my I
thought you have gone to college I'm too
young for college silly we think we saw
something in the playground not too long
ago what is it has it been found well we
haven't started looking for it yet okay
everyone nap
[Music]
time guys let's go look for the monster
huh wait what I agree I can't stop
thinking about it let us for go and let
the two babies sleep all right let's do
[Music]
this where was it that way it was really
huge and it had things it was right here
Zoe we promise it's gone let's go back
in guys was it blue with a crown yeah
how'd you know cuz it's right behind you
guys it's a
blue oh no get him huh get him
ow he's in the
[Music]
trash that's funny
m